govnokri.com 2016-06-11

# latest Privacy Policy govt jobs 2016 upcoming 2015 recruitment notification

**[www.ingovtjob.com](http://www.ingovtjob.com/)** Really takes your Privacy Seriously. This Privacy Policy Describe what personal Information do we collect and how we use it.

We Collect information from you when you subscribe to our posts or Comments.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: E-mail Address.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google as and content network privacy Policy.

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

– To send periodic E-Mails

The E-mail address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/ or other requests or questions.

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers Hard Drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser setting. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by containing customer service.

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the LAW, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non – personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

By using our site, you consent to our websites Privacy Policy.

If we decide to change our privacy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on 15th July 2013.

If there are any questions regarding this privacy Policy you may contact us using the information below.

 **Govnokri@gmail.com**

Important Note: Kindly Visit to official website to get detailed information about this post as above information on this page may not be complete.
